stbaldricks.org 2008-09-26

# St. Baldrick's Foundation - About St. Baldrick's - Contact Us

  * **MAILING & DONATION ADDRESS**  
1443 E. Washington Boulevard, #650   
Pasadena, CA 91104-2650

If you are unable to donate online, you may donate by phone or mail. Please Click Here to select the shavee, barber or team you want to support, and print the donation form to send in, or call: 888-899-BALD.

  *  **PHONE**  
(888) 899-BALD 
  * **FAX**  
(626) 792-3081 
  * **FOUNDATION WEB SITE**  
www.StBaldricks.org
  *  **INFORMATION**  
  * **WEB SUPPORT**  
  * **MEDIA**  
If you are a member of the media and need more information, please email your contact information and the details of your request to [Media@StBaldricks.org](mailto:Media@StBaldricks.org) and one of our staff will contact you. 
  * **DISCLAIMER**  
The St. Baldrick's Foundation is dedicated to supporting medical research and quality of life advances for children with cancer. It does not provide medical advice, information about specific patients or medical or cancer care.
  *  **PRIVACY POLICY**  
  
This privacy statement applies to the St. Baldrick's Foundation with respect to the privacy of our online visitors and donors.  
St. Baldrick's does not collect personally identifiable information without permission. This site collects contact information when you donate or register. In such cases, we will need personal information such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card number, in order to register your participation, process your donation, and/or provide a receipt. We may use the information you provide to send you information about event results, how proceeds are being distributed and other St. Baldrick's related promotions.  
St. Baldrick's periodically performs statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of various areas on our website and to use such information to improve on our website's ability to serve you better. Personally identifiable information collected in these surveys will not be shared.  
Our website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Our web server is located in a locked, secure environment. All databases containing personal information are securely stored on a separate system.  
Our server is encrypted to protect credit card and other information submitted via the forms on this site. St. Baldrick's follows the Association of Fundraising Professional's (AFP) Ethical Guidelines to the Code of Ethical Principles and Standards of Professional Practice.  
To protect your privacy, the St. Baldrick's Foundation does not sell, rent, exchange or otherwise share information about donors, shavees or other participants with any other organization or individual.   
St. Baldrick's will discontinue contact with any person upon oral or written request. Those wishing to opt out of receiving communications from St. Baldrick's may contact: St. Baldrick's Foundation, 1443 E. Washington Blvd., # 650, Pasadena, CA 91104-2650, or phone 1-888-899-BALD, or e-mail sbinfo@StBaldricks.org. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us.
